Contact

sanja1mandic@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sanja-mandic-823995a2 (LinkedIn) sanja42.pythonanywhere.com/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Leadership
Time Management
Contract Management

Sanja Mandic

Full-Stack Software Developer Serbia

Summary

Find my projects on @https://github.com/Sanja969
Mechanical engineer and a full-stack developer, with a great interest in new technologies and innovation. I am a dynamic person, open to new knowledge and experiences. I love working on my own or as part of a team and I try to motivate others around me. My goal is always to accomplish the assigned tasks and reach the highest levels of performance possible, as well as to help people grow and improve. Open to new opportunities.

Experience

Microverse Student Mentor Software Engineer April 2022 - Present (3 months) San Francisco

Remote

- Mentoring new students who are joining for Full Stack Web Development Course.
- Support mentees on their rigorous journey in the BootCamp from personal to technical difficulties.
- Provide continuous support through one-to-one video conference calls to mentees
- Help and prepare a structured roadmap for mentees to efficiently finish their curriculum
- Developing web apps following CI/CD (GitAction workflow) using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, React JS, and Ruby On Rails as backend.
- Meet weekly and monthly deadlines.

Velesstroy, Moscow Lead Planning Engineer August 2018 - September 2021 (3 years 2 months) Moskva

3D modeling in Autodesk Revit

Analyzing a construction schedule

Creating construction timeline in NavisManage via connecting tasks in the schedule with objects in the 3D.

Analyzing contracts with subcontractors and making a Business plan

Tracking the actual norm from a construction site and connecting different
databases using power pivot add-in in excel for output report

BEXEL Consulting
Designer
August 2017 - June 2018 (11 months)
Beograd

3D modeling in Revit

Pneumatik flex Technical Sales Engineer April 2017 - August 2017 (5 months) Serbia

Purchasing raw and reproductive materials,

Contacting all available Suppliers,

Making a decision which is the most appropriate part (raw, reproductive materials, fittings..) for the required system considering all information and quality certificates given by contacted suppliers,

Control of the arrived goods as well as control of received invoice,

Making the Quantity and the Quality receiving report,

Developing sale opportunities and building rapport with customers,

Provide technical information and explanation to all parties,

Considering Request for Inquiry and forming Inquiry with information,

Creating manufacturing orders based on a purchase order

Feniks BB

Production Engineer February 2015 - March 2017 (2 years 2 months)

Niš, Centralna Srbija, Serbia

Duties and Responsibilities:

Construction of Control valves, Regulating balancing valves, 2-way and 3-way valve, selection of purchased parts, making part lists for new products, coding of all parts and assemblies and its administration on the company server.

3D Modeling and 2D drawing (making technical documentation) in software program NX –

Siemens PLM program (CAD module) of Control and Regulating balancing valves for all their parts

and assemblies.

2D drawing in AutoCAD software program.

Testing of developed valves on the test station and measuring of its characteristics, making

reports (data collection, writing reports, making tables and diagrams) and its representation.

Designing and installation of the new testing station - selection of all parts and equipment,

hydraulic calculation of pipelines, determination of the characteristics of the pipe network and making technical documentation.

CNC G-Code Programming.

Design, develop and control documentation of QMS according to ISO 9001: 2008.

Education

University of Belgrade, Mechanical Engineering Master's Degree, Automatic control (2008 - 2014)

Pozega, Technical school

High School, Mechanical technician for computer designing · (2003 - 2007)